so i'm about to start views from mandolin i'm very emotional this morning because i feel a
change happening within me i can feel my vibration rising i've been really committing myself to doing
a lot of work physically mentally spiritually etc and um and then i got a response from jewel's and
not only is he okay he said he would love to talk and i want to just say to you all when i made the
video yesterday referring to jewels and what he said about reading so many people had just mean
things to say and nothing about my video even invoked that there was no energy of mendacity
there was no energy of acrimony whatsoever and i want you all to ask yourselves why did you feel
so comfortable just being mean because i had to ask myself that at a point in my life
apparent in my life why do i feel so comfortable being mean and we tell ourselves it's just our
opinion etc etc but a lot of times it's not even it's just it's just it's just you saying something
to make yourself feel better it's not like floyd mayweather who is somebody who can't read is also
like posting a woman's abortion records and also like running around with israel you understand what
i'm saying but i i noticed how many people just felt compelled to just be dicks i don't want to be
that and i look forward to talking to sanzanna
i'm excited